<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Secondary Entities on Documaster Noark5 API</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/model/secondary-entities/</link><description>Recent content in Secondary Entities on Documaster Noark5 API</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/model/secondary-entities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common Entities</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/model/secondary-entities/common-entities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/model/secondary-entities/common-entities/</guid><description>Common entities are shared entities which provide additional context to the core entities. The set of entities detailed here are :
External ID (EksternId) Keywords (Noekkelord) Notes (Merknad) External ID ExternalID (EksternId) is a common entity which allows associating business system specific identifiers to Documaster archived entities. This way the business systems can retrieve different entities from the archive using their own identifiers, rather than keeping Documaster archive specific IDs.</description></item><item><title>National Identifiers</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/model/secondary-entities/national-identifiers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/model/secondary-entities/national-identifiers/</guid><description>National identifiers enttities allow associating different Norway specific identifiers to both folders and records.
Address (Adresse) Building (Bygning) Property (Eiendom) Plan (Plan) Diagram showing the relation of the national identifiers entities to any other entities through its reference fields. The diagram depicts the most important set of fields, leaving some of the use cases out of it for simplicity. Address Address (Adresse) is an entity representing an address.</description></item></channel></rss>