<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Other Operations on Documaster Noark5 API</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/</link><description>Recent content in Other Operations on Documaster Noark5 API</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Lists Operations</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/codelists/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/codelists/</guid><description>Overview Code List operations are used to manage the different lists of values used for fields of the core entities. Definition of the code lists can be found in the Data Model section of the documentation.
Important to notice is that the API works with code lists associated to core entity types and specific fields.Entities fields names are unique in Documaster Archive and are the unique identifiers of the code lists.</description></item><item><title>Business Specific Metadata Operations</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/bsm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/bsm/</guid><description>Overview Business Specific Metadata operations allow full control over the additional metadata that can be added to extend the core Noark5 entities. Business specific metadata can be added to the following set of core entities :
Class (Klasse)
Folders
Basic Folder (Mappe) Meeting Folder (Moetomappe) Case File (Saksmappe) Case Party (Sakspart) Records
Basic Record (Registrering) Meeting Record (Moetoregistrering) Registry Entry (Journalpost) Correspondence Party (Korrespondansepart) Document (Dokument)</description></item><item><title>Bulk Operations</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/bulk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/bulk/</guid><description>Overview Bulk operations allow control over large set of entities for opening and closing them. The operations listed below are technically changing the status of the modified objects, thus limiting the possibility of any future changes.
POST /noark5/v1/bulk/open The operation is used to open a parent entity and all of its child entities recursively. The operation returns immediately and execution of the requested change is done in an asynchronous way.</description></item><item><title>Full-Text Search</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/full-text-search/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/full-text-search/</guid><description>Overview Full-Text Search operation allows querying the archive using an arbitraty string over a predefined collection of entity types grouped in index collections or as referred to in the operation paratemers doctype. Entities created in Documaster are indexed on a regular basis and available in those index collections for full-text queries to be executed.
Index Collection Name Indexed Entities Tekst Tekst (document text)Dokumentversjon (latest only)DokumentAbstraktRegistrering (and its Noekkelord, Korrespondansepart, virksomhetsspesifikkeMetadata, secondary Klasse, and secondary Klassifikasjonssystem)AbstraktMappe (and its Noekkelord, virksomhetsspesifikkeMetadata, primary Klasse, secondary Klasse, secondary Klassifikasjonssystem, Sakspart, Arkivdel, and Arkiv) Korrespondansepart Korrespondansepart Registrering AbstraktRegistrering (and its Noekkelord, Korrespondansepart, virksomhetsspesifikkeMetadata, secondary Klasse, and secondary Klassifikasjonssystem)AbstraktMappe (and its Arkivdel, and Arkiv) Mappe AbstraktMappe (and its Noekkelord, virksomhetsspesifikkeMetadata, and Sakspart) Arkivdel Arkivdel Using the index collection Tekst would be the default for most of the use cases related to full-text search.</description></item><item><title>Logs Operations</title><link>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/logs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://documaster.github.io/api-docs/operations/other/logs/</guid><description>Overview Logs operations are used to query the different logs available on the archive side - change log, access log, download log.
POST /noark5/v1/logs/change-log The operation is used to retreive the change log entries for a specific archive entity instance.
HTTP Request Field Location Mandatory Type Description Authorization Header yes string access token aquired as part of the authentication call, prefixed with Bearer X-Documaster-Error-Response-Type Header yes string custom header indicating that any error should be reported in JSON format, rather than the standard text format, should always be provided as application/json $.</description></item></channel></rss>